Sheldon, I do hope you forgive me
for my inappropriate behavior last night.
(Sheldon:)I don't blame you.
(Sheldon:)-You were intoxicated.
-Thank you.
(Sheldon:)I blame Penny.
(Penny:)I blame Penny too. Bad Penny.
(Leonard:)Wait a minute, what are you talking
about? What inappropriate behavior?
(Beverley:)-I think it's best that you not know.
-Agreed.
(Sheldon:)Agreed.
(Leonard:)What the hell, agreed.
(Beverley:)And I want you to take very good care
of this young woman.
-Aw. Thank you, Beverly.
-You're welcome.
(Beverley:)She doesn't have much
in the way of career prospects.
(Beverley:)Don't make her responsible
for her own orgasms as well.
(Leonard:)Remember when I was complaining that
you don't communicate with me enough?
(Beverley:)-Yes, dear.
-I'm over it.
Fa-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.